websitespromotiondirectory.com 2009-03-07

# -

## Websites Promotion Directory 

### Privacy Policy 

Introduction

Websites Promotion Directory respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how any personal information you provide on our site is processed and used by us. This privacy policy is designed to protect you, our users, by informing you what personal information is collected, what we do with that information, with whom we share it, and the methods we use to collect it. Your use of the "Websites Promotion Directory" website is subject to your agreement with this policy.

Information we collect

Simply put, our function is to facilitate your efforts to submit your website to our directory so the collection of personal information is limited to your name and email address and is always voluntary.

In all cases, no information submitted by a buyer will be shared, sold, reused in lists, or be used for any other purpose than to complete a transaction or address a customer service concern.

We do not try to collect any further data when submitting your website for review.

Payment information is processed through a third party credit card processor and is not collected by "Websites Promotions Directory". Our processors do not share, sell or otherwise use personal information for secondary purposes.

We also do not sell or pass on your personal details to third parties without your consent, except in the following, highly unlikely, instances: 

  * where it is required by applicable law or pursuant to a court or similar order  
  * where it is required for the purposes of obtaining legal advice or for the purposes of, or in the course of, legal proceedings to which "Websites  
Promotion Directory" is a party or a witness.        

"Websites Promotion Directory" also contains links to websites operated by third parties. These links are meant for your convenience only. Links to third party sites do not constitute endorsement on our part of those sites and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of the owners and operators of those sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies on each site which asks you to submit personal and contact information.  
Conditions of use and revisions

By accessing or submitting your website for review to the Websites Promotion Directory you consent to the collection and use of information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. Your use of the "Websites Promotion Directory" is subject to your agreement with this Privacy Policy.  
Queries

If you have any queries regarding this Privacy Policy, you can contact us via email.
